SAY NO TO PIRACY, SUPPORT ORIGINALS
ADAPTED FROM THE ORIGINAL WEB NOVEL
THE EARLY SPRING, BY GU NIANG BIE KU
Where were you?
I went to make a call.
Sun Yu.
Wake up.
One more round!
One more?
Where's Yao Bei?
She said she wanted to head back
to pack her luggage.
Then, she left.
Right.
She got promoted.
She's going to Hong Kong, China.
- Promoted?
- She's leaving Beijing.
I almost forgot to tell you this.
I got promoted too.
Don't tell me you're leaving Beijing too.
No.
No way.
I'm not leaving until I get
a three-bedroom, one-living-room flat
in Beijing.
Don't leave.
- No.
- None of you can leave Beijing.
If you leave, no one will keep me company.
Don't worry.
I won't leave. I'll grow old with you.
Pinky promise. None of you can leave.
We'll stay in Beijing
and make our dreams come true.
Make our dreams come true together.
Don't go.
Yes.
Already passing out?
Come on. You guys are boring.
I'm just getting started,
and you guys are out cold.
Lumi.
Do you have a boyfriend?
So many of them.
I'm sure you can have more.
We have a blind date event tomorrow.
Come check it out.
You can get any guy you want.
I want one who looks like Eddie Peng.
Eddie Peng?
You might have encountered
a pig-butchering scam.
You don't have a guy like that?
Why bother mentioning it then?
BEING WITH YOU IS LIKE A LEAP OF FAITH
Morning.
Morning, Tao.
You're so early today.
- Morning.
- Morning, Lumi.
You're back in full force.
You even put on red lipstick.
We partied until so late last night,
I almost couldn't wake up this morning.
I agreed to be there for Sun Yu's event,
so I dressed up a bit.
Oh, the girl with the red sweater?
The matchmaker?
Yes.
Don't go to her matchmaking event.
Why not meet up
with my childhood friend first?
I'm just there to show support,
not for the blind date.
When you're there this evening,
check out the guys for me.
See if there's someone like Eddie Peng,
like what your friend said.
If you find one, keep him for me.
Sure.
- Morning, Mr. Luan.
- Boss.
Morning, Luke.
Luan Nian.
I want to hold onto you.
LUKE: LUMI, COME TO MY OFFICE
Come in.
Boss. How can I help?
How is the progress of the proposal
that you and Shang Zhitao are working on?
I told her to submit it tomorrow.
She has a blind date today.
A blind date?
Yes. She can't work overtime
every day, can she?
We must all live our lives. Right, boss?
Do you know why you work overtime?
Because you don't focus on work
during office hours.
I need the proposal today.
Luke.
Come with me.
My work is done.
Overtime.
You want the proposal?
I already sent it to Lumi.
There is something else. Come.
The seat belt is stuck.
Thank you.
Have you gotten the driving license?
I got it last month.
I'll take you to practice driving.
You will participate in Yueteng's
new car test drive event.
So by working overtime,
you mean I need to practice my driving?
I mean I'm working overtime
to practice with you.
Sorry, I can't be there.
Emergency overtime.
Take the wheel. I'll sit next to you.
Practice with your car?
Don't you have a driving license?
Pull your seat forward.
Practice.
Go now.
You were so eager to leave work today.
Who were you planning to see?
My flatmate.
You have a blind date with your flatmate?
Just how did you get your driving license?
Let me go out and check.
No need.
I'll drive.
Sorry.
You haven't answered me.
Who do you have a blind date with?
Are…
Are you jealous?
You wish.
My flatmate
works in the marketing division
of a dating website.
So I--
It was an accident.
You had an accident, I know.
But what about Luan Nian?
Was he also an accident?
First, he saved you,
then, he created the happy accident.
The way I see it,
he has been playing the long game.
Date a few people.
Experiment a bit while you're young.
We only live for around 30,000 days.
If you like someone, tell them.
If you miss them, go see them.
As long as we're safe
and it's what we want,
we have nothing to lose.
If you want,
we can keep our relationship private.
You…
You don't wear pajamas?
You're wearing mine.
I'll return them to you later.
I want them now.
I have to go home.
I have work tomorrow.
Sure.
Let me call Mr. Liu. He'll drive you home.
- Don't.
- Mr. Liu.
Sorry for calling you this late.
Can you send someone home for me?
Yes, she's at my home.
What?
I don't want him to drive me back.
He'll recognize me.
So, what do you want?
I'll sleep in the guest room.
Planning to disappear tomorrow
without saying goodbye
and just leave me a small note?
I won't leave you a note this time.
Last time, it was an accident.
But this time, it's not.
What is it then?
I don't want to lose my job.
I don't want to jeopardize my job either.
I don't want others to think
I'm taking shortcuts
by relying on you.
I'll sleep in the guest room.
You're making it more obvious.
Can you
drop me off at the subway?
Eat first.
You made this yourself?
It's delicious.
Can I have one more glass?
Yes.
Thank you.
Just drop me off
at the subway entrance in front.
JINTAI XIZHAO SUBWAY STATION
We missed it.
It's pouring. No need for the hassle.
No one's around at this time.
Just go up first.
SHANG ZHITAO
Floor One.
Coming up from the parking lot?
Did you buy a car?
No.
Sun Yu gave me a ride.
Your friend is so much better
than my boyfriend.
It's raining,
and my car is restricted today,
and he didn't even offer
to give me a ride.
Doesn't your boyfriend always pick you up?
He's quite considerate.
What's the point of having a boyfriend
if he's not considerate?
I have to deal with a mean boss
with a weird temper
at work already.
Dealing with another one after work
will make my life miserable.
Where were you last night?
You didn't even change your clothes.
You're making it so obvious.
It's not even a big deal. Just show it.
Linda from Sales
always shows off her sexcapades.
- Boss.
- Morning, Luke.
Sun Yu is that good, huh?
Was he as amazing as she said he was?
Introduce him to me.
- I'll gauge him for you.
- Enough…
Stop guessing.
My laptop is…
What's wrong with your laptop?
I left my laptop in Sun Yu's car.
I need to call her
and ask her to bring it back.
I'll go to Luke then.
What for?
I'll tell him
you didn't go home last night.
Don't. What are you telling him?
Why are you so scared?
Are you traumatized by him or what?
We'll be talking about the proposal.
He couldn't care less
about the man you saw.
Shouldn't you check with Alex
first about the proposal?
Yikes.
Thank you for the reminder.
Otherwise, I would've been scolded.
Alex comes in late.
I'll get a cup of coffee.
Do you want anything?
No, thanks. Go. I'll make the call.
Brandish it.
Luke.
I left my laptop bag in your car.
I'll bring it to you later.
No need.
I'm at the parking lot.
I'll find an empty place and wait for you.
Parking lot emergency exit.
I'm there.
When you come in, stomp your feet twice.
Even an arms smuggler
isn't as cautious as you.
Thank you.
What are you afraid of?
I don't want people to see us.
We must maintain a distance at work.
And you maintain the distance
by inviting me
to a dark staircase?
Shang Zhitao.
Let's date in secret.
Okay.
But you can't tell anyone about us.
Including your friends,
your family…
and your colleagues.
Especially at the office.
You are my superior,
and I am your subordinate.
Fine with me.
We'll remain exclusive to each other.
I'll come see you every Friday.
Okay. It's Friday today.
- See you in a bit.
THIRD FLOOR
Hi, Mr. Luan.
During my second year in Lime,
he and I started dating in secret.
If coming to Beijing
is my first leap of faith,
then this secret weekend relationship
is my second leap of faith.
This relationship makes me more mature,
but it is also addictive.
SANYUAN BRIDGE
BUSINESS DIVISION 2
BANNER AD, CPI COST PER IMPRESSION
PC PAY PER CLICK
IMC INTEGRATED MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS
Luke.
Let's go back together.
But we must maintain a distance.
I don't want people to see us.
Just go first.
I haven't finished my report yet.
It's raining.
I'll drive you back.
You can finish it at home.
Eyes on the road.
Does your cute flatmate
always come down to pick you up?
Hmm?
‪I…
Not every day.
He does that if I come home late
because the staircase is quite dark.
And it's not just me.
He does that to others too.
We help each other out.
I'll walk you up.
No need. I can just run there.
I need to know your unit number.
When you were drunk last time,
I couldn't find your unit.
Okay.
I'm home.
You can go back now.
Your clothes are wet.
I want to see you go inside.
They are asleep.
Let me see you off.
WELCOME HOME
Shang Zhitao.
Your mascara is smeared.
As agreed,
see you on Friday.
You're on my hair.
Sorry. Hush.
The board.
Surprise!
Happy Birthday.
SHANG ZHITAO, HAPPY BIRTHDAY
Sun just came back.
We want to make up for your birthday.
Yes. Happy Birthday.
Your nose. You got whipped cream on it.
Oh my.
I'll get the cutlery.
Let me help you.
Your mascara is smeared.
Your boss drove you home.
Let me look at the cake.
LUMI
Hello?
Luke. The logo inside Yueteng Auto Show
promotional pamphlets
is misprinted.
Fortunately, we found out in time.
We don't need to reprint everything.
Tomorrow, I'll bring Flora with me
to deal with it in person.
The person in charge is Flora?
Yes.
Let's hear her solution for this first.
Three days until the show.
Let me reassure the client first.
- See you at the office.
- Okay.
SHANG ZHITAO
LUAN NIAN
Tao. Your phone is ringing.
Pick it up for me. My hand is wet.
Hello?
I'm looking for Shang Zhitao.
Okay. Hold on.
He sounds urgent. You should answer it.
Hi. Who's calling?
It's me.
The logo inside Yueteng Auto Show
promotional pamphlets is misprinted.
I'm on my way to your home.
Come down in five minutes.
We'll go back to the office.
YUETENG AUTO
Your overtime tonic is here.
Coffee.
Just go.
I'll send it to your inbox
once I amend it.
I'll stay with you.
You have to work overtime because of me.
Who would have known
that the client would ask us to change
the size and the logo at the last minute?
I have amended it and sent it out.
Okay. Thank you so much.
You got the client's logo wrong?
How did you communicate
with the design team?
Come up with a solution now.
What's the matter, Tao?
I have to return to the office.
Careful.
TIANTONG DONGYUAN
Luke.
Sorry.
I sent the wrong version.
Tonight, I'll use our supplier database
and find a supplier near the show venue
to reprint the pages with the wrong logo.
I can assure you that the problem
will be solved before the launch.
Who sent the email?
You or the design team?
I… It's me.
I am the person in charge.
I should be held accountable.
I am willing to accept the punishment.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Shang Zhitao.
This is a grave error.
According to the company policy,
you will not be promoted
or receive a pay raise for a year.
Are you sure about it?
Okay.
LIME SUPPLIERS LIST
This…
Sorry for calling you this late.
Sorry for the trouble.
YUETENG AUTO DC QUICK CHARGER
PURE JOY, BOLD SPIRIT. YUETENG AUTO
Well, I have a date
with my girlfriend tonight.
I have to go now.
Sure. Thank you.
2013 BEIJING AUTO SHOW
SHUNYI NEW VENUE
YUETENG AUTO
13TH BEIJING INTERNATIONAL
AUTOMOTIVE EXHIBITION
BEIJING SUBWAY BATONG LINE
TONGZHOU BEIYUAN STATION
Yueteng Auto Show was a success,
but during the project,
a huge error occurred.
The logo was misprinted.
This is because
I did not double-check
before sending it to the supplier.
As the project manager,
I take full responsibility.
I accept any punishment from the company.
But the situation was salvaged in the end.
Flora worked very hard in this incident.
She worked overnight for two days
to change the pages with the wrong logo.
The client did not suffer any losses.
That's right.
No one is perfect.
It's Flora's first time
as a project manager,
and she handled it calmly.
It's an achievement.
If it involves our clients,
it's our priority.
And never repeat this kind
of simple mistake again.
But Flora did come up
with a solution in time
to salvage the whole situation.
I'll tell Tracy
that, as a punishment,
she will not be promoted
or get a raise within six months.
Her bonus for this quarter will be halved.
Dismissed.
You didn't cause any losses.
Why did he punish you?
Tao.
Cheer up.
He's just giving you a warning.
You will have your bonus.
It's not about the bonus.
That means you're taking it to heart.
You think he's cold and heartless.
To settle this matter, Luke
reassured the client in person.
He also approved the budget
for reprinting personally.
This is his leadership style.
He holds us to a high standard,
but he still protects us.
Don't take it to heart.
Lumi.
Thank you for helping me clear this mess.
Thank you for defending me.
Thank you for consoling me.
You want to thank me?
Smile for me.
Smile properly.
Tao, you're back.
You haven't eaten, have you?
Lei made seafood fried rice today.
I saved a bowl for you.
Come eat.
You didn't come home for two days.
You must be tired.
Lei's cooking is still as good as usual.
It's all your favorites.
You're so nice to me.
Of course.
Why wouldn't I?
- It's so good.
- Right?
I had two bowls.
All good at work?
Yes.
I knew you could do it.
Good. I'm glad it's settled.
Eat.
But I won't be promoted for six months.
Six months?
Seriously?
That's way too harsh of him.
Even if he wasn't your boyfriend,
as a boss, that was so cruel.
I did make a mistake.
It's just that I don't know if I'm upset
because he scolded me as my boss
or because he didn't give me
any special treatment.
But if he did
give me any special treatment
and show favoritism,
it wouldn't be what I wanted.
But he…
I know you're someone
who knows what's what.
But we are emotional creatures.
It's fine if we can't be
completely rational.
Don't be so harsh on yourself.
Crybaby.
Maybe I'm just too weak.
I hope
I can be stronger.
Just like him.
That way, we can communicate
on equal footing
and keep work and personal life separate.
So how strong do you have to be
to realize that in the relationship?
I don't know.
I hope I can improve
a little bit every day.
All right.
Don't dwell on it.
Just sleep.
Tomorrow is a new day.
Eat slowly.
Your hair.
As the project manager,
I take full responsibility.
I accept any punishment from the company.
YOU GOT THE CLIENT'S LOGO WRONG?
HOW DID YOU COMMUNICATE
WITH THE DESIGN TEAM?
COME UP WITH A SOLUTION NOW
To settle this matter,
Luke reassured the client in person.
He also approved
the budget for reprinting personally.
This is his leadership style.
He holds us to a high standard,
but he still protects us.
THANK YOU
ACTUALLY, I…
Hello?
Where are you?